# SWAPNALI MORE

San Francisco, CA 94107 +1 (415) 832 9453 - swapnalim182@gmail.com

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Self-motivated Developer adds high level of experience over more than 3+ years collaborating and working on multiple web-based projects. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. Organized approach to meeting multiple, concurrent deadlines. Pulls from active knowledge of current technology landscape to promote best practices in web design.

#### SKILLS

- React/Redux
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS/SCSS/LESS
- Bootstrap/React Bootstrap/Material
   UI
- REST
- Node JS/Express JS
- MySQL/MongoDB

### Work History

## 04/2022 to Current

## Senior System Engineer(React)

**Infosys Ltd.** - Pune, MH

- Worked with advance web development technologies like React, ECMAScript
   6, Typescript, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, SCSS, JavaScript Object
   Notation.
- Validated customer interface requirements and assessed impact of needs on available systems.
- Collaborated on stages of systems development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases.
- Discussed issues with team members to provide resolution and apply best practices.
- Participated in software field testing to verify performance of developed projects.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Maintained high-level expertise in React state management strategies.
- Designed reusable and reliable code for use within distributed cloud environments.

- Designed intuitive graphical user interfaces to improve user experience.
- Designed REST calls using React to streamline user interface performance.
- Developed software for desktop and mobile operating systems.
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.

#### Front End Developer 09/2020 to 03/2022

## Neosoft Technologies - Mumbai, MH

- Researched emerging web technologies and trends for possible incorporation into sites.
- Advocated for well-tested and documented, high quality code.
- Worked cooperatively with client services, sales and design team in deadlinedriven environment.
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customer.
- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Teamed on user-centric design strategy in translation of UX and business requirements into coded solutions.
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Planned and engineered RESTful web services to manipulate dynamic datasets.

## 05/2019 to 09/2020

# Web Developer

### Kush Infosystems Pvt Ltd - Mumbai MH

- Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS for integration and cross-browser compatibility.
- Communicated with product managers and UX designers to translate project requirements and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Built highly functional web applications using JavaScript, HTML and CSS.
- Used wireframes, mock-ups and prototypes to establish user interface design and architecture.
- Verified program logic using testing and debugging best practices.
- Devised site maps and mockups for designs based on proven methodologies and end-user feedback.

#### **EDUCATION**

09/2018

Master of Science: Computer Science Mumbai University - Mumbai MH

02/2016 Bachelor of Science: Computer Science
Mumbai University - Mumbai MH